Extract personal relevant entities, and their relations. Return only the jsonl format list .

Ontology: 
- relations: {"acquaintance", "children", "other_family", "parents", "siblings", "spouse", "place_of_residence", "visited_place", "pet", "residents_of_place", "visitors_of_place"}
- types: {"ORG", "GPE", "PERSON", "DATE", "EVENT", “ANIMAL”}

Input:
[
"User: My daughter, Emma, recently moved to London.",
"Agent: That's exciting! Does she like it there?",
"User: Yes, she loves it! She even adopted a cat named Whiskers.",
]

Output:
[
{'x': 'User', 'x_type': 'PERSON', 'y': 'Emma', 'y_type': 'PERSON', 'r': 'children'},
{'x': 'Emma', 'x_type': 'PERSON', 'y': 'London', 'y_type': 'GPE', 'r': 'place_of_residence'},
{'x': 'London', 'x_type': 'GPE', 'y': 'Emma', 'y_type': 'PERSON', 'r': 'residents_of_place'},
{'x': 'Emma', 'x_type': 'PERSON', 'y': 'Whiskers', 'y_type': 'ANIMAL', 'r': 'pet'},
{'x': 'Whiskers', 'x_type': 'ANIMAL', 'y': 'Emma', 'y_type': 'PERSON', 'r': 'pet'},
]

Input:
[
"User: Alice moved to Munich.",
"Agent: That's interesting. What does she do there?",
"User: She works for Google.",
"Agent: And what is your relation to her?",
"User: She is my sister."
]

Output: